http://www.sfstl.org/donate/privacy-policy/

Donation Privacy Policy
Revised – July 6, 2017
The Scholarship Foundation of St. Louis, a 501(c)(3) nonprofit organization, is strongly committed to protecting the privacy of its donors, students, volunteers, staff and website users. This policy identifies what personal information is collected by this website and the organization and how the information may be used.
The Scholarship Foundation of St. Louis does not sell, rent, share or otherwise provide personal information collected to anyone outside the organization unless otherwise requested by you, the donor. For example, your personal information may be used to respond to your requests or to process your donations. The Foundation maintains appropriate electronic and physical safeguards over its systems to prevent unauthorized access and/or use.
The Scholarship Foundation does not collect personally identifiable information from individuals unless they provide it voluntarily and knowingly. You can visit the Foundation website without telling the organization who you are or revealing any personal information. The Foundation employs Google Analytics to collect nonspecific, non-personal information for the purpose of analyzing website traffic and improving content. Most browsers allow the user to deny or accept the cookie feature.
The Scholarship Foundation of St. Louis has contracted the services of Stripe to process credit card donations and to insure that all credit card information submitted through this site is safely and securely transmitted over the web. The Foundation does not record or store your credit card information when donations are submitted on-line.
This website includes links to external websites. These links are provided for additional information on related topics or for educational purposes only. These links do not fall under the control of the sfstl.org domain and sfstl.org is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of external websites. The Scholarship Foundation of St. Louis makes no representations or warranties with respect to any linked website. Your use of any linked website is solely at your own risk.
Email Privacy Policy
Revised July 6, 2017
The Scholarship Foundation utilizes automated systems for mass email communication to deliver emails to members of our mailing lists. If you have received a mailing through one of these systems, The Scholarship Foundation has identified you as “opting-in” to the mailing list. This means you—the holder of this email address—have: (a) voluntarily shared your address with the Foundation for the purpose of receiving information or (b) registered with the Foundation, made a donation, or otherwise have an existing relationship with The Scholarship Foundation or (c) explicitly granted permission to another organization to share your address with its business partners which include The Scholarship Foundation.
Together, The Scholarship Foundation and its automated email vendors use security measures to protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of data used by our system. These email vendors will not share, sell, or rent any information about you without your expressed, written permission, unless compelled to do so by law. Every mass email communication contains a link at the bottom: “Review/Edit Your Account Information or Unsubscribe.” Click this link and follow instructions to unsubscribe or edit/review your account information.
The Scholarship Foundation reserves the right to amend its privacy policies at any time. Therefore, please review them periodically. Use of the website after changes to the policies will be deemed to be your agreement to the changed terms.
For additional information about this site, to ask questions about these privacy policies, or to review or correct personal information collected by The Scholarship Foundation of St. Louis, please contact the Foundation by phone, in person, or through our website.
DonateMake a Donation
Planned Giving
Integrity
Privacy Policies
Donate Now
Tribute Gift
Recent ArticlesAnother test post for LSATest post for LSAStudent Loans: Five Years of Amicable DivorceStepping Forward, Stepping Up2020 Endorsements from a ProphetArchive Archive
Select Month
December 2020  (2)
November 2020  (2)
October 2020  (2)
September 2020  (2)
August 2020  (2)
July 2020  (7)
June 2020  (5)
May 2020  (3)
April 2020  (5)
March 2020  (7)
February 2020  (5)
January 2020  (2)
December 2019  (2)
November 2019  (9)
October 2019  (3)
September 2019  (1)
August 2019  (7)
June 2019  (1)
May 2019  (3)
April 2019  (2)
March 2019  (2)
February 2019  (2)
January 2019  (2)
December 2018  (1)
November 2018  (1)
October 2018  (2)
September 2018  (6)
August 2018  (2)
July 2018  (1)
June 2018  (2)
May 2018  (5)
April 2018  (3)
March 2018  (8)
February 2018  (5)
January 2018  (5)
December 2017  (4)
November 2017  (4)
October 2017  (3)
September 2017  (2)
August 2017  (4)
July 2017  (5)
June 2017  (13)
May 2017  (8)
April 2017  (3)
March 2017  (3)
February 2017  (1)
November 2016  (2)
October 2016  (1)
September 2016  (1)
August 2016  (2)
June 2016  (4)
May 2016  (1)
April 2016  (3)
March 2016  (1)
February 2016  (5)
January 2016  (1)
December 2015  (3)
November 2015  (1)
October 2015  (2)
September 2015  (1)
August 2015  (8)
June 2015  (1)
May 2015  (4)
April 2015  (2)
March 2015  (4)
February 2015  (3)
January 2015  (12)
December 2014  (9)
November 2014  (2)
October 2014  (1)
September 2014  (1)
August 2014  (1)
June 2014  (3)
May 2014  (1)
April 2014  (1)
February 2014  (3)
January 2014  (2)
December 2013  (1)
November 2013  (3)
October 2013  (5)
September 2013  (2)
August 2013  (1)
July 2013  (2)
June 2013  (1)
May 2013  (3)
April 2013  (1)
March 2013  (2)
January 2013  (1)
November 2012  (1)
August 2012  (1)
July 2012  (1)
June 2012  (3)
May 2012  (1)
March 2012  (2)
February 2012  (1)
